Fan service
Should we go with A set?
Sure, anything's
fine for me
But when is
the president coming?
She's almost here
Who is it?
Ah, it's Soobin
Look at this
[I took it on my way home!]
I guess he's doing well
Wow, that's cool
Right?
You must be starving
Did you order
something?
Yes, we ordered A set
The most expensive one
Long time no see
Congratulations!
You're on public TV now!
Oh, don't say that…
I'm feeling
pretty happy, though
It feels like
I'm stepping up
You did a great job
Congratulations
But, is that rumor
about Shin Yoo-il true?
The contract
termination lawsuit…
Why do you bring that up
all of a sudden?
Can't we just talk
about that?
Well…
the penalty would be
quite a lot, right?
It depends on
Shin Yoo-il's decision
But President Goo
wouldn't want
Shin Yoo-il to leave
the company either